Hello
and welcome back!
I'm finishing getting ready for the day right now, which is why my makeup is
half done, but welcome back to a new vlog.
I actually have not vlogged in a very long time.
I've been kind of A, inconsistent with posting, and B, just working on videos that
I have filmed from earlier in the summer or like from last month essentially, but
it is actually September 1st, so happy September.
I'm really excited.
September is my favorite month of the year besides October.
Those two months are my favorite and so I literally woke up so excited this
morning that it's September.
I hope everyone had a great summer and a great August.
With that being said, obviously we are now back to school.
I did have my first week back to fashion school last week, which is really,
really nice.
I felt so good just being back on campus and having like a structured schedule.
I actually kind of love school.
My attention span is not the best, but I do enjoy especially what I'm learning,
which if you're new here, I'm at Fashion Institute of Technology, which is a fashion
school in New York, and I'm studying advertising and marketing communications there, which is really,
really cool.
It's a lot of like digital marketing, and a lot of people tend to go
into PR with this major, so it's really cool.
I really enjoy it, and now I'm in my bachelor's as opposed to last year
when I was completing my associate's.
Actually, I have two associates, you guys.
Yeah, so it's really cool.
And now it's like getting a little bit more, not advanced, detailed, I guess you
would say.
So it's really interesting.
I'm excited.
I like my classes so far.
It was just a good week, but I wanted to like make sure I settled
in properly before taking you guys along.
I also did end up like switching out some classes.
So whatever I had last week is not exactly the same as going forward.
Anyways, so it's actually Labor Day today, meaning there is no school, but I'm gonna
take you guys through a school week in my life.
Also, I don't know if you can peep in the mirror reflection, a little new
addition to the apartment.
That is a little hint to the video that I'm currently filming because it's one
of the many additions I'm making to my apartment.
So stay tuned.
I'm not just going to ignore it that there's like new things happening in the
apartment.
Kind of rambling, but I did want to catch up with you guys because I
genuinely feel like I haven't sat down to like talk and film.
It felt like all of August I wasn't vlogging.
I don't know why, but nonetheless, we are here and I'm excited for this new
start of the year.
I've heard so many people say this and I totally agree.
Sometimes September 1st or like the start of a new semester, if you're a student,
feels more like a fresh start than New Year's Eve does.
I totally agree.
I personally think like every time September rolls around or like end of August, I'm
like, it's a new year, new me, like that sensation.
And I love it.
It's just exciting.
There's like something different in the air.
So I hope you guys enjoy this week's vlog and my first back to school
vlog, if you will.
Let's have a great week, a great September and get into our plan.
Okay,
good morning you guys.
It is.
Ha!
I need to leave.
7.51.
Let's go to school.
I need to put on my lippy, my lip combo, but I do want to
show you guys my outfit before I leave.
I've been loving just doing simple outfits and then dressing it up with accessories.
It's like the easiest formula, so I don't have to overthink my outfit for school.
So today we have just a simple, classic white tank.
This is from Koss.
I'm obsessed with it.
It's like the thickest, nicest ribbed material.
Probably my favorite white tank I've ever bought.
I really recommend it.
And then my gorgeous jewelry from Pilgrim Jewelry.
They kindly sent me these pieces.
I'm literally obsessed.
Look at the earrings, you guys.
So cute.
Sorry, I'm talking really fast because I'm a little late.
These jeans are from Ragged.
This belt, I could not tell you.
And then these are my little Jeffrey Campbell boots that go all the way up.
Cute stuff.
Okay, I feel really good.
I have two classes today.
A lunch break in between, which I'm going to spend doing some work, editing, all
that stuff.
I need a band-aid.
You guys, I want to show you.
Well, actually, it's kind of disgusting i don't really want to show you my finger
has gotten really dry i think like one of my rings started to like be
too tight on it so now it's like super dry and i have to constantly
put neosporin on it and on top of that that same finger i just broke
my nail there so the whole pointer finger looks so disgusting anyways this is chaotic
let's go
Thank you.
Okay, obviously back home.
I'm just stopping by to change into my workout outfit I'm headed to a new
workout class that I've never tried before.
It's in Tribeca, I believe.
I forget the name of the place But I don't think it's like traditional Pilates.
It's not I don't think so I literally don't know what I'm getting myself into
but I just wanted to sign up and take myself to a little workout class
like A Pilates fusion something we're gonna see I hope it's nice because I've been
sitting on my butt all day and I need some like energy.
Um, so we're going now.
School today flew by though.
I was like, how is the day already over?
And like, even during my lunch break, I was like, it's already time for my
second class.
Like, I don't know.
I just went by fast, which I'm not really complaining about.
It was a good day nonetheless.
And yeah, now I'm excited to just go move my body a little bit, to
be honest.
5.25.
I mean, there's just no way.
Oh my god, I don't want to touch anything.
I didn't film in there at all because, I don't know, I just never feel
really that comfortable filming in workout classes.
Amazing.
I literally was like, okay, I'm at Pilates class, like, how hard can it be?
I'm going to be so sore tomorrow, but in the best way possible, I'm really
glad I did it.
And it was actually so relaxing too.
And it was like different like functional movements that also really stretched the body and
like released a lot of tension that we hold in like our hips.
And I literally was like two pound weights and I was like shaking and so
out of breath.
Good morning
you guys, it is Wednesday.
I only have one class today, which is nice and it's like a shorter class
because I have it twice a week.
Classes at FIT, by the way, are three hours long minimum usually.
But yeah, this class is like, it meets twice a week as opposed to just
once a week.
So it's like a shorter class today, which is nice.
But I still dread it.
I really don't like this class.
It's like some computing, financial, mathematics, everything I don't like.
essentially it's just like boring to me whatever anyway let's pick out my outfit i
don't know what to wear today i never know what to wear nowadays because when
you're in school some classes are like super hot some classes are like really cold
it'll say it's like nice out and then it'll end up being like really windy
and freezing and then other times it's like oh it's cold but then the sun
comes out of nowhere and you're like sweating your ass off yeah that's the dilemma
i've been having the last week and a half so i don't really know what
to wear let's see what i can whip up i am getting ready to go
to campus and just like hang out there until my class later and then i'm
just gonna work at a cafe until then okay i think i wanna wear these
black jeans from motel rocks i've been loving these lately they just have such a
nice like silhouette and i don't know they're really good jeans really good jeans and
then i could do this top from my mom made it she's cute let's see
what i settle on if i like this combination together i'll come back to you
guys with my final outfit decision not wear a single thing that i just pulled
out and showed You guys my whole outfit is thrifted today actually shout out depop.
Love you.
I'm very pinkalicious today I love it keeping it simple today with the jewelry perfume
i showed this perfume in a recent video because i went to the like showroom
this is by dossier the it factor perfume i'm obsessed with it it smells so
good i like doused myself in it okay dolls we are ready to go work
a little bit and then we're gonna head to class.
Okay, I just finished my one and only class of today and I was going
to head home.
I have a lot of chores to do today so I was going to avoid
stopping in then because nobody wants to see me do laundry.
But I'm actually walking over to H&M because it's close to campus and I'm just
going to go see what they have to decorate my home.
So
Happy Friday everyone.
I obviously did not vlog yesterday.
It was kind of like not a mundane day, but I was like it's gonna
be repetitive if I vlog again.
I don't know.
Anyways, I had two classes yesterday one of which is a video studio production class
that is my longest class yet it is four hours it's like in the later
part of the day so I'm kind of like I was literally falling asleep but
it's really cool we get to like be in this studio and yesterday we were
playing around as both on the crew side of things and the technical part and
then also me and my friend were in front of the camera for a little
bit pretending to be like a host and a guest on a talk show and
we're live it's such a fun class it's really like hands-on and really cool but
today on Friday I don't have any classes which is really really nice.
I'm gonna use today's to be a little bit productive.
I have to go ship out a Depop order.
Somebody bought my boots.
Thank you for buying my boots because I've been trying to get rid of these
Doc Martens forever.
And I recently went to Home Goods and I bought these cute boxes.
Like how adorable is this?
And then it came in another one.
Literally adorable.
And I've been wanting to gift my mom and my sister a lot of the
products that I receive in PR and don't personally use or that has just been
like piling up and my sister recently moved into college so like the house is
completely empty now so it's been an adjustment for both my mom and my sister
and I thought it'd be sweet to just kind of ship out these surprise gift
boxes and I also bought these like little cards from home goods that says you
can do this I'm gonna write a little note and just give them some like
products that I think they would really love they have no idea I'm doing this
so I'm really excited for them to receive it so let's see what we can
whip up.
Okay, so this is like the big, it's so heavy, the box that I keep
most of my PR products in.
Oh my god.
Starting off, I gave my sister most of the Sol de Janeiro perfumes.
She loves these, but last time she came, she couldn't bring this home because it
was over the like limit of lights.
I received this like acne skincare line, which I've used quite a bit of, but
she loved the products that I didn't end up using.
So I'm gonna give her this pore shrinker toner.
She literally asked for it last time that she was here and like visited and
I was like, I kind of want it and then I didn't use it.
Also gonna give her some highlighters from Ofra Cosmetics.
She had been asking me like, oh what are some good highlighters?
This will be perfect for her.
This one as well that has some bronzing shades.
She loves anything glowy in terms of like skincare makeup so I'm gonna give her
this Kosas Glow IV Vitamin Infused Skin Enhancer.
Also these wildflower stickers I think she's really gonna love.
A Mario Badescu lip mask.
For my mom, I'm gonna give her this Kosas bronzer.
It's super beautiful shimmery bronzer.
Also, this Patrick Ta plumping gloss in the shade Need Her.
Super pretty.
This Kosas Dream Beam Comfy Smooth Sunscreen.
It's like a shimmery, super lightweight sunscreen.
Really nice.
And then I'm trying to debate which clock clip to give to my sister.
My mom doesn't use clock clips, so there's no point.
I think I'm still gonna give her this one.
I feel like she would love it.
And she has so much hair.
She's really gonna appreciate the bigger clock clip.
These are from Chell Chells, by the way.
Super cute.
And then also for my sister, I'm going to give her these like cute heart
earrings from telegram jewelry Let's package up these little cute boxes and then write the
notes and ship them out
I have my return from Amazon and my Depop order in here.
And here are the two gift boxes.
And then I also have to run some errands.
I think I have to go to like Target.
And I'm getting my nails done later because that's horrifying.
Let's go ship these out.
you
guys
it's almost 3 p.m and i have not left
my house today but that isn't to say i wasn't productive i definitely was productive
i just now i really need to get out before i like lose my mind
a little bit i need some fresh air i also have a lot of work
to do i have some homework and also some like work videos to edit, a
YouTube video to edit.
Yeah, I also just wanna like plan out my week.
I got a new planner.
I never had a planner.
I don't think I have at least, maybe when I was like really little.
I've never had a proper planner, so I got this one and the sheer elegance
of it makes me so excited to actually use it.
Like it is ridiculously beautiful.
The layout too is really nice.
You can do a monthly reflection and then for the month that's coming up, a
little roadmap like personal goals and habit trackers.
It's just been a game changer and like it's helping me be more organized with
school and even like little things that I have going on during the week just
so I don't forget because my brain is always like scrambled and I've tried using
like digital planners and things like that I just never stick to it I end
up just like typing in my notes so this has been amazing I'm gonna go
ahead and plan the week out and have it all clearly laid out I think
we're gonna go to my OG cafe it's to go there all the time during
first semester it's on the upper east side and I'm never in the uppers like
during the school especially during the school week because like my school is in Chelsea
and then like a lot of what I do is like downtown so I'm never
up there and it's so peaceful.
I feel like for this Sunday.
It's like super gloomy outside It was like raining all of yesterday raining a little
today.
I feel like that would be so cozy It's like a hot coffee or something
Yeah, I could not be bothered to put on makeup today So I'm using these
glasses as like a little as a little makeup essentially.
All right, let's go
so
Thank
you.